<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on It&#39;s All About Me</title>
    <link>http://glennhasa.website/categories/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on It&#39;s All About Me</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;#169; by Glenn Dixon</copyright>
    <atom:link href="http://glennhasa.website/categories/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Favorite Tweets</title>
      <link>http://glennhasa.website/favorite-tweets</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://glennhasa.website/favorite-tweets</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I just ran across a really well-worded and humorous tweet on Twitter, and my first thought was to retweet it using the new ‘quote tweet’ feature on Twitter. Unfortunately that doesn’t seem to work on mobile platforms yet, so I went to my desktop and pulled it up on Tweetdeck.Twitter.com. I started to say something like “I want to frame this tweet and hang it on my wall” but of course I have no printer and my apartment walls are concrete, so…then I thought about digitally framing it. What would that look like? Is there a service like that already out there?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, according to Google, no. So I Googled how to just simply embed Tweets and the top highlighted result was actually an internal Twitter help page. So I copied the code but still had nowhere to put it. I have long-dormant Tumblr, Storify, and RebelMouse accounts, but I can’t muster the energy to dust them off. So I thought maybe I’ll just throw it into a blog post. And then it hit me – what about a separate category and archive stream for these on my own site? Bingo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And here we are…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;twitter-tweet&#34; lang=&#34;en&#34;&gt;&lt;p lang=&#34;en&#34; dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/BradMossEsq&#34;&gt;@BradMossEsq&lt;/a&gt; Yes. You&amp;rsquo;re right. You&amp;rsquo;re truly talking parallel universe. Peopled by unicorns all tripping on acid. &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/KenDilanianAP&#34;&gt;@KenDilanianAP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; RoundaboutWheel (@emptywheel) &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/emptywheel/status/596422571379269634&#34;&gt;May 7, 2015&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async src=&#34;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Except that tweet didn&amp;rsquo;t look anything like a Twitter card display. Is it just me, or does this seem like something that should be more automatic? And then I migrated my site to Markdown files using Jekyll and Github Pages. And look at that - the Tweet looks just as intended. Evidently something as simple as this requires an extra plugin on WordPress. No wonder the geeks have all migrated away from it&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How My Wife Cured Her Type II Diabetes</title>
      <link>http://glennhasa.website/how-my-wife-cured-her-type-ii-diabetes</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://glennhasa.website/how-my-wife-cured-her-type-ii-diabetes</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Diet is just one letter away from die.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For most of man&amp;rsquo;s existence it was all about staying alive long enough to have kids and keep the species alive. You ate what you could, when you could. We come from a long line of hunter-gatherers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At some point things shifted (at different times around the world) and we began settling down, growing crops and raising animals. And then a couple of hundred years ago we figured out how to mass produce staples such as flour and sugar and changed everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The big question is, from an evolutionary standpoint, how long does it take for man to adapt to changes like this? Are our systems still fine-tuned for hunting and gathering, or are they fine-tuned to allow us to adapt to whatever circumstances we find ourselves in? That is the conundrum we face when we look at today&amp;rsquo;s landscape of dietary advice. And it&amp;rsquo;s confusing as hell to the average person who doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a degree in evolutionary biology or nutrition or any sort of scientific field. I&amp;rsquo;m basically trying to sort through all of this myself, and this article is me just writing it down. Maybe it will turn out to be helpful &amp;ndash; we&amp;rsquo;ll see.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As it currently stands, there are a few basic viewpoints that today&amp;rsquo;s dietary advice proceeds from. Here are the main ones, as I see it:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conventional Wisdom. This view generally ignores evolution and proceeds from there. Think &amp;lsquo;Food Pyramid.&amp;rsquo; Obesity is caused by too many calories and too much fat. Calories in, calories out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Low Carb. Gary Taubes&amp;rsquo; book popularized it. Carbohydrates, mainly processed sugars and flours, wreak havoc on our endocrine systems and are responsible for obesity and Type II diabetes, etc. Paleo diets are an offshoot of this, adding in a cave-man exercise concept.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I grew up as the medical community was adding a low-fat component to conventional wisdom. But obesity grew, and the answers as to why seem elusive. Here are the valid observations, as I see them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Segregated native populations world-wide historically suffered very rarely from gallstones, kidney stones, cardiovascular disease, obesity and cancer, the so-called diseases of modern (Western) civilization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;These populations had very diverse diets, from the high-fat Inuits to fruit and veggie tropical populations to high-carb Indonesians.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All of these populations get the diseases of Western civilization after being exposed to the Western diet, especially processed flours and sugars.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At the same time, modern agriculture and medicine have allowed our population and life expectancy to mushroom.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many of these problems stem directly from obesity, so most of the focus has gone toward solving that problem. And therein lies the rub, because while there are dozens of proven ways to lose weight the general population just keeps getting fatter. For many years, most dietary methods were variations on the same theme - eat less, lose weight. Unfortunately this rarely lasted, in part due to food manufacturers doing everything they could to keep your hunger and cravings ramped up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gary Taubes&amp;rsquo; writing on this topic proposed a radical variation. His premise was that different types of calories produced different types of processes in the body. His conclusion was that carbohydrates should be minimized, and indeed multitudes have successfully lost weight using this general concept. But why? Is it really because a shift in macronutrient percentages triggers your body to store less fat, or is it something else? &lt;em&gt;What, exactly, is the underlying mechanism?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the longest time I believed Taubes&amp;rsquo; theories. The wife and I are long-time low-carbers, and by that I mean that we&amp;rsquo;ve generally adhered to the concept while not always actively eating that way. Our first real success with any form of sustained weight loss was on Atkins (the original book) around 1998-99. I still haven&amp;rsquo;t revisited my low weight from that time period, although I&amp;rsquo;m currently within 10 pounds of it. [UPDATE: I have now been below 200 for several months] For most of the last decade we&amp;rsquo;ve hovered in a range closer to our max weights than our low weights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After reverting from our original Atkins success, we just assumed we could lose back down easily by restarting Atkins, but time has proven otherwise. Taubes&amp;rsquo; writing reinforced our beliefs re: carbs over the years, and we even spent awhile doing zero-carb, meat-only, which &amp;lsquo;worked&amp;rsquo; but was expensive to maintain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A couple of years ago my wife was diagnosed as a Type II diabetic. Her blood sugar levels were &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; high. Regular testing has shown that carbohydrates do, indeed, spike her post-meal blood sugar levels. But what are the underlying mechanisms at work here? Conventional wisdom would say that her pancreas and/or liver are simply failing to produce enough insulin - a genetic flaw, in her case, as she is not obese. Taubes, et al, would say that a lifetime of processed foods has damaged her body&amp;rsquo;s ability to produce insulin. Carbs has caused her diabetes, in other words.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Until recently I was resigned to this line of thinking. My wife was destined to watch her carbs closely and eventually she would have to start taking insulin as her Type II slowly, inevitably morphed into full insulin dependency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But then science stepped in and upset the apple cart.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One way of treating obesity that has proven successful is bariatric surgery. The fact that it is an invasive surgery has limited its use to only those patients who are morbidly obese. I always thought it a very inelegant solution to the problem, but it definitely helped people lose weight and extended their lives. And it had a very surprising result for diabetic patients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many morbidly obese candidates for this surgery are also Type II (adult-onset) diabetics on some form of medication. After bariatric surgery most of them experienced a normalization of their blood sugar levels and many were eventually off their meds and experiencing complete remission. One study showed that as many as &lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;3&lt;/sub&gt; maintained this state for five years or more. The fact is that their pancreas and livers had not lost their ability to produce insulin, as some had speculated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These results tore a bit of a hole in Taubes&amp;rsquo; theories. His writing indicated that it was a lifelong overload of carbohydrates that permanently damaged the ability of the pancreas and liver to produce insulin, eventually leading to a diabetic state. But bariatric patients with a 10-year or longer history of diabetes were experiencing normal insulin levels without the aid of any medication - technical remission! But while this disproved Taubes&amp;rsquo; mechanism theories, it did not directly prove any other mechanism. Subsequent theories have targeted chemicals in gut flora somehow being triggered by the severe diet restriction in and around the surgery, but the details are not clear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One group at Newcastle University in the U.K. came up with a different concept, something they refer to as the Twin Cycle Hypothesis. To test it they decided to skip the actual mechanism and simply attempt to mimic the results. Since insulin recovery often occurred in bariatric patients long before any weight loss, it was theorized that perhaps it was simply the caloric restriction that set things in motion, resulting in a removal of fat around the pancreas and liver. To test this they put patients on an 800-calorie diet for 8 weeks. The results were very similar to those observed in the bariatric patients! This line of thinking/testing has resulted in some very clear guidance, at least on &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ncl.ac.uk/magres/research/diabetes/reversal.htm&#34;&gt;Newcastle University&amp;rsquo;s web site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So Dixie basically thought &amp;ldquo;Hey, why not?&amp;rdquo; So she spent eight weeks eating an average of around 700 calories per day, mostly veggies combined with shakes from GNC. And no, not &amp;lsquo;protein&amp;rsquo; shakes. Her diet ended up being around 50% carbohydrates. I can&amp;rsquo;t begin to tell you how amazed I am at her willpower. She even stuck with it when she was hit by some sort of amoebic or parasitic intestinal invasion. Her bowels recovered. She lost quite a bit of weight too! She is definitely more thin than she has been for the last 20 years or so. But the real question is, what about her Type II Diabetes?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She took her blood glucose readings all during the diet. The numbers all dropped, but the real test was what would happen when she went off of her Metformin. So she stopped taking it the day after her diet ended.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amazingly, her blood glucose levels are all still in the normal range, both when she first wakes up in the morning and after meals. So far, it appears to have done the trick. No more medicine, no more fear that her longevity might be in danger. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Technically, she&amp;rsquo;s not diabetic any more!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;UPDATE: It has now been about a year since Dixie started her 2-month diet. She still occasionally tests her glucose levels &amp;ndash; sometimes first thing in the morning, sometimes after meals. All readings are still in the &amp;lsquo;normal&amp;rsquo; non-diabetic range. Her HBA1C bloodwork from the lab confirms the same.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Not To Do Customer Support</title>
      <link>http://glennhasa.website/how-not-to-do-customer-support</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://glennhasa.website/how-not-to-do-customer-support</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Recently oDesk and Elance began completing their merger. The new site is called &lt;a href=&#34;http://upwork.com&#34;&gt;Upwork&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As can be expected, there are glitches and resets. The first thing that caught my attention was when my email inbox started receiving a &lt;em&gt;LOT&lt;/em&gt; more email notifications than usual. So of course I logged in to Upwork and went to the notifications page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sure enough, every single possible notification was turned on. So naturally I attempted to customize these to my preferences, and that&amp;rsquo;s when the problems occurred. When I attempted to save the settings, a white, opaque window popped up with an animated spinning icon. The spinning never stopped, the settings never saved. When I reloaded the page all boxes were still checked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I tried logging into the site using a browser I had never used on this new Upwork site before, Internet Explorer. Same result. This led me to opening a support ticket, mainly to let them know that there was a problem to be fixed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In response, I got a canned email talking about browser caches and cookies. On top of that, the ticket was closed with a presumption of being resolved!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also tweeted a link to this blog post, and in fairly short order the @UpworkHelp account responded with an actual, official explanation of the problem. No, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t me - it is a known issue being worked on by their engineers. It&amp;rsquo;s been an issue since the switchover. This matches what I had suspected, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t give me any greater confidence in their support procedures. I&amp;rsquo;m now &lt;em&gt;less&lt;/em&gt; worried about the future viability of this company, but my confidence in my ability to get timely, actually helpful support is still pretty low&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kill The Music Industry</title>
      <link>http://glennhasa.website/kill-the-music-industry</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://glennhasa.website/kill-the-music-industry</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last night we finally got around to watching &lt;a href=&#34;http://alexwinter.com/&#34; title=&#34;Yes, That Alex Winter - aka Bill, of Bill and Ted fame!&#34;&gt;Alex Winter&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rsquo;s documentary &lt;a href=&#34;http://downloadedthemovie.com/&#34;&gt;Downloaded&lt;/a&gt;. Once you see it, you&amp;rsquo;ll realize how ironic it is that you can actually &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.spin.com/2013/09/downloaded-napster-documentary-stream/&#34;&gt;stream the movie online&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s mainly about the history of Napster and the guys who started it, but from behind the scenes. For most of us, all we knew about the whole incident was what the music industry wanted us to know. Pirates were stealing money from artists, and they must be stopped. As is common, the truth behind the scenes is a whole lot more complicated than that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And by complicated, I mean that the music industry is full of lying, scumbag pieces of shit! But more on that in a moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Part of this issue is about business models. The music industry reached their heyday built on record labels for talent acquisition, management, recording and marketing, radio stations for publicity, record stores for retail sales and concerts for some additional publicity and branding. Also, the concert tour is where the artists could make enough money to pay back their advances and maybe actually make some decent money. It was usually enough to encourage them to make their next recording and start the cycle over again. The &amp;lsquo;single&amp;rsquo; 45rpm recording got you to pay for two songs when you only wanted one. The album did the same but with you paying for 10-12 songs when you wanted maybe only 3-4 of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of this was beginning to shift by the time Napster came along in 1999. Now it&amp;rsquo;s in full swing. You can stream most anything, and if you can&amp;rsquo;t you can buy it through several online services. The price is low, the product delivery is instant. Musicians can find each other locally or online, record at home, distribute and market their recording directly to the fan online. They can also book tours directly. Everything is sold one song at a time, and you never have to buy a song you don&amp;rsquo;t want. And even if you pay very little for the music, or get it for free, the band makes money on merchandise and experiences (concerts).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This movie documents how the industry fought tooth and nail to stop all of this from happening. In the end, they slowed it a bit, but they missed an incredible opportunity. Napster had financing and FIFTY MILLION users! They could have been an industry-controlled iTunes. Instead, the RIAA and Hilary Rosen burned it to the ground, and sealed their own doom in the process. Napster was replaced by a dozen clones, the number of people sharing music outside the normal channels actually &lt;em&gt;increased&lt;/em&gt; and all it took to kill all that was to make it easy to download music priced reasonably. That&amp;rsquo;s how Steve Jobs did it with iTunes and iPods, and later the smartphone. The RIAA shot themselves in the foot, and it looks like the patient is terminal. In the meantime, the millenials generation has shifted from owning songs to giving their time and attention to songs and artists. The measure of success is attention and sharing, which translates into merchandise and ticket sales, and sponsorship money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those times when a band needs some money to live on while they aren&amp;rsquo;t on the road, the crowdfunding model has become very successful. Once you get some street cred, fans will actually pre-purchase enough music and other items to cover your time in-between concert tours. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/user/jackcontemusic&#34;&gt;Jack Conte&lt;/a&gt;, of &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.pomplamoose.com/&#34;&gt;Pomplamoose&lt;/a&gt; fame, co-founded &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.patreon.com/about&#34;&gt;Patreon&lt;/a&gt;, which allows fans to become &amp;lsquo;patrons&amp;rsquo; for their favorite artists in many genres. It&amp;rsquo;s part of the trend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After watching the movie, I came away with a particular animosity for several people and entities:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The RIAA and music labels, naturally. I was motivated to be sure that I never gave them any of my money, ever again.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Metallica - I&amp;rsquo;ve never been a big fan but I did like a few of their songs. Now I&amp;rsquo;m committed to see them fade away into a well-deserved obscurity, hopefully one without royalties.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hilary Rosen - this is an evil person. She has gone on to help defend BP from the massive oil spill in the gulf and to try and push SOPA through Congress. She is now a lobbyist with a long list of White House visits. FUCK her.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m glad to see Shawn Fanning was able to go on and make some good money from other efforts. And, of course, Sean Parker has had insane success with Facebook and Spotify. Many others in the movie have gone on to other companies and careers. It&amp;rsquo;s a really great movie, and if you ever downloaded music before iTunes, you should see it. And hey, it&amp;rsquo;s free! You&amp;rsquo;ll come away from it with a better sense of just how much of a massive shift the internet is to music and musicians, and hopefully a desire to support your favorite bands.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Legend of CoyoTejano</title>
      <link>http://glennhasa.website/the-legend-of-coyotejano</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://glennhasa.website/the-legend-of-coyotejano</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;OK, let&amp;rsquo;s be honest. There isn&amp;rsquo;t much of a legend. The nickname basically came out of some friendly banter with the workers at our favorite watering hole down here in ol&amp;rsquo; Mexico. I&amp;rsquo;m a lifelong Texan (tejano in Spanish) and someone mentioned coyote and I combined them into one nonsensical word. It&amp;rsquo;s been my nickname there ever since.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m experimenting with this whole &amp;lsquo;put your blog on GitHub&amp;rsquo; thing. I&amp;rsquo;m currently using the static site generator Jekyll and the GitHub Windows client.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So we&amp;rsquo;ll see how this goes, I guess.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Photo Sharing Service That Killed Google and Flickr</title>
      <link>http://glennhasa.website/the-photo-sharing-service-that-killed-google-and-flickr</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://glennhasa.website/the-photo-sharing-service-that-killed-google-and-flickr</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;tl;dr The service I found for unlimited storage of and easiest sharing of embedded photo albums is, quite surprisingly, the service best known for ridiculous meme photos. I&amp;rsquo;m moving my &lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; Terabyte of photos and videos there as you read this&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s the bottom line. Now, to explain myself and how this incredible turn of events came about&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A bit of background - Dixie and I quit our jobs and hit the road four years ago. We thought of it as a mini-retirement, but we ended up settling down in Mexico for a few years. We will begin traveling again at some point in the future, but in the meantime we&amp;rsquo;ve compiled a massive set of photos and video, from Alaska to New York City to Costa Rica. I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure we are approaching &lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; Terabyte of files. That&amp;rsquo;s like 500 Gigabytes. Yes, that is a ridiculous number.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://cdn.meme.am/instances/500x/23774466.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Y U Post Too Many Pictures?&#34; /&gt;
{: .img-right } I will have things set up for Dixie to be able to finish sorting, deleting, editing and uploading all of our photos, a task we abandoned early on in our travels. It&amp;rsquo;s a lot of work, especially if your tools and storage solutions aren&amp;rsquo;t ideal. At different times we have stored photos on Google (Picasa) and Flickr and Facebook, and a few temporary uses of Photobucket. But we have &lt;em&gt;way&lt;/em&gt; too many files to simply dump on our web server where our blogs live. The cost would quickly go through the roof. The one solution we used most frequently was Flickr, usually alongside various WordPress plugins to make things easier to insert and embed. And since Flickr is now free for up to 1 Terabyte of space, it seemed like the best solution going forward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few days ago I started seeing a lot of talk about Google&amp;rsquo;s announcement at their recent I/O conference. Evidently Google Photos is now unlimited for free. I doubt we&amp;rsquo;ll ever need more than a Terabyte online, but I did a quick review and a comparison between the new Photos service and Flickr. And that&amp;rsquo;s when I hit a big snag&amp;hellip;&lt;em&gt;I couldn&amp;rsquo;t figure out how to embed a photo album from either one&lt;/em&gt;! And we&amp;rsquo;re not talking about a tech noob here - I&amp;rsquo;ve built dozens of web sites! And if it&amp;rsquo;s something &lt;em&gt;I&lt;/em&gt; find difficult, I really worry about how difficult the workflow will be for Dixie. Right now it appears to be actually &lt;em&gt;impossible&lt;/em&gt; to embed photo albums from either service, and that appears to be by design. They really want you to visit their site. You can embed slideshows, sort of, but sometimes maybe you want to stop and look at a photo without having it slide off the screen. Sometimes maybe you want to skip some photos and go to a specific one. That&amp;rsquo;s my preference, and that&amp;rsquo;s what I went looking for. And I found my solution in a very unlikely place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://i.imgur.com/vU1LEQB.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Imgur &#39;good boy&#39; meme&#34; /&gt;
{: .img-left } For those of you who aren&amp;rsquo;t familiar, Imgur has long been the realm of memes, the cute, crazy images with funny captions, similar to the one I used here. It was an early favorite with the kids on Reddit and Digg. I&amp;rsquo;ve used the service before, mainly as a quick way to share a screenshot, but that&amp;rsquo;s about it. So you can imagine my surprise when I discovered the following facts about Imgur:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can create a user account&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can upload &lt;em&gt;unlimited&lt;/em&gt; photos!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can choose several different ways of embedding albums.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, I should show you an example. I haven&amp;rsquo;t uploaded anything yet, except for one album which is basically pictures of grass with some stone walls peeking through. Not particularly entertaining. So here&amp;rsquo;s a much better example of what you can do with Imgur. Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe class=&#34;imgur-album&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; height=&#34;550&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; src=&#34;//imgur.com/a/twP6C/embed?background=f2f2f2&amp;text=1a1a1a&amp;link=4e76c9&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>